[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What element was usually the subject of transformation in alchemy?", "correct_answer": "Lead", "incorrect_answers": ["Copper", "Lithium", "Tin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are badgers related to weasels?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately, how many species of dolphins exist?", "correct_answer": "40", "incorrect_answers": ["20", "30", "12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the artifact that Indiana Jones steals from the tomb raiders in the cave, loses it,  and then recovers it 26 years later off the Portuguese Coast?", "correct_answer": "The Cross of Coronado", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sword of Coronado", "The Cross of Cortez", "The Sword of Cortez"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the hound dog in the romantic comedy Sweet Home Alabama?", "correct_answer": "Bryant", "incorrect_answers": ["Coach", "Earl", "Bubba"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kakapo is a nocturnal parrot indigenous to New Zealand. Due to its resemblance to this nocturnal animal, it is also called by its name.", "correct_answer": "Owl", "incorrect_answers": ["Raccoon", "Cat", "Rat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Mosss battalion in Vietnam in No Country for Old Men?", "correct_answer": "Twelfth Infantry", "incorrect_answers": ["Sixth Infantry", "First Infantry", "Fifth Infantry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This astrological sign, ruled by Pluto, has the reputation of being highly sexual. Persons born under it, usually feel emotionally secure if they are financially settled.", "correct_answer": "Scorpio", "incorrect_answers": ["Aquarius", "Sagittarius", "Leo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not an actual name of a sea?", "correct_answer": "Blue Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Red Sea", "Yellow Sea", "White Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brontophobia is the fear of thunders.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This man invented the alarm clock so he could awake at 4 A.M. every morning.", "correct_answer": "Levi Hutchins", "incorrect_answers": ["Satori Koto", "Jonathan Larson", "Seth Thomas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The person who developed the popular game Sudoku was from which country?", "correct_answer": "Switzerland", "incorrect_answers": ["South Korea", "Malaysia", "Japan"]}]